hi 👋 how are you doing?
I come to supermarket
to top up some groceries today
cherry tomato ¥199
cucumber 🥒 3 for ¥98
golden kiwi 🥝 ¥98
one more
egg ¥228
organizing …
I found this AN (red bean) BUTTER SAND cookies ¥556
it looks delicious, I have to try 🤤
boiled Udon ¥128
cut chicken thighs from Kagoshima ¥500 each
they are very good value today 👍
these pork belly slices are in good value too!!!
Akita grown pork belly slices ¥500 each pack
I think I will get one more pack of chicken thighs 😅
thin fried tofu ¥ 108
MOMEN (hard) tofu ¥58
NATTO with beans from Hokkaido ¥108
milk also from Hokkaido ¥178
sausage ¥288
UNAGI (eel) from Kagoshima ¥999
the eels are in good value too 🤩
so I will get two !
white bread 🍞 ¥168
focaccia bread 🥖 ¥158
hot dog 🌭 roll ¥138
here is better 😅
milk pudding ¥99 after 50% discount
it looks yum 😋
I will get another two
who doesn’t like a discount right ? 🤣🤣🤣
oh I spotted new ice cream 🤩
I have to try!
pumpkin flavor PARM ¥98 each
this is also new I think
Mango GARIGARI KUN ¥78 each
animal cookies ¥150
the cookies has English name of the animals
done shopping 🎶
I come to Daiso to buy school and house supplies
Daiso is a good place to shop for stationery too
found what I want 🎶
B5 index dividers
A4 paper
B5 blank paper
3 colors white board makers
small note book
one more
note pad
there are many smartphones accessories in Daiso too
so cute 🤩
smart phone stand ?
looks so useful
while we bring our own shopping bags nowadays
we have to buy the plastic bags for rubbish
such an ironic right …😏
this is the largest here in Daiso
citric acid for cleaning 🧽
there is a Miffy corner here
paper plate
oh they are so adorable 😍
Miffy aluminum foil
Miffy baking sheet
gloves that can be tightened
this looks good
I can use my phone with the gloves on!
perfect for YouTuber? 😆
I have to patrol the Halloween 🎃 corner of course
oh the banners are so cute ☺️
and the stickers too 😍
I better leave before I grab anything here 😅
I’ve never tried this what so called basil seed, is it nice?
the boys love this Natadecoco drink ( white grape flavor)
so I will get for them again (pineapple flavor)
butter peanut 🥜
the boys all 👨🏻🧑🏻🧒🏻 like prawn flavor  rice cracker
chips that used olive oil from SHOTOU Island
the basket is getting heavy 💦
done shopping at Daiso 🎶
after I done some house chores
I come to Gyomu Supermarket
carrot ¥99
cucumber 🥒 ¥299
Eringi mushroom ¥99
there is a lot in the bag!
Daikon ¥99
I’ve never seen this peer ¥350
the sign says “SANSEIKI NASHI”
HOUSUI peer ¥199
one more
cabbage ¥99
Shimeji mushroom ¥128
crab stick ¥55 each
blueberry 🫐 yogurt ¥78
one more
yogurt drink ¥188
custard pudding ¥188
fish cake stick with squid ¥68
fish cake ¥68
bacon 🥓 ¥495
black sesame seed ¥88
potato starch ¥88
ready made meat dumplings 🥟 ¥378 each
they are ¥20 cheaper than usual, I will get another two
the boys all love this, it will be gone in a blink 😅
matcha Kit Kat ¥198
consommé flavor chip ¥74
done shopping 🎶
I am going to top up my groceries
apple 🍎 is cheap today!
¥98
persimmons are new in the season
but let’s get one and try
¥128
Enoki mushroom ¥88
egg ¥228
ground pork ¥580
chicken thighs from Kagoshima ¥893
plain yogurt ¥138
one more
small baguette 🥖 ¥238
white bread 🍞 ¥168
one more
tuna ¥288
what is this?
blue Fanta ?!
and it’s a mystery 😅
I will get for the boys 😙
¥88
tacos chip ¥108
one more
done shopping today🎶
I come to Gyomu supermarket 🛒
what will I find today …?
potato 🥔 from Hokkaido ¥199
Daikon ¥99
should I get the peer or persimmon…?
I will get the peer
umm these two look more yellowish 💛
Korean lettuce leaves
only ¥49 !!!
sunny lettuce ¥99
chicken wings from Aomori ¥1043
pork slice from Aomori too! ¥1204
yogurt drink ¥188
blue berry yogurt that S likes ¥78 each
fish balls ¥68 each
fish cake with squid 🦑 ¥68 each
sesame oil ¥698
KADOYA JYUNSEI
Kinu Tofu (soft type tofu) ¥29
seafood cup noodles ¥108
just looking at all these make me hungry 🤤
pizza 🍕 from Italy 🇮🇹
chapati 🫓 from India 🇮🇳
lagsana from Spain 🇪🇸
beef & cheese pie from Australia 🇦🇺
I will get this pizza crust ¥348
I think I am going to use it for Halloween 🎃
Chip Star salt flavor ¥78
the apple pie 🥧 look delicious 🤤
crepe from Netherlands 🇳🇱
egg tart from Portugal 🇵🇹🤤
bubbles tea and potato sweets from Taiwan 🇹🇼🤤
I need to clear up my freezer so I can get all those items
cloudy day always make me a little down
and with a sick husband at home, I need to top up groceries
season of persimmon now 🤩
persimmon with no seed ¥99
one more
small pumpkin for Halloween decorations 🎃
next to the chestnuts 🌰 are Shine muscats
I struggle a little but decided to get it
usually fruit at the end of their season is not as good
but let’s give it a try ¥880
cherry tomato ¥199
Chinese chives ¥158
onion 🧅 ¥129
meat buns ¥495 after 10% discount
egg 🥚 ¥228
one more
chicken thighs from Tokushima prefecture ¥757
they are really good value today 🤩
so I will get one more pack ¥770
ground beef & pork ¥680
they are good in value too, I think I’ll get one more
ham ¥278 each
sausage ¥298
stick cheese ¥178
cheese from Netherlands and Germany ¥578
milk from Hokkaido ¥178
plain yogurt ¥138
I haven’t eaten breakfast this morning….
getting hungry looking at all the bread 🥯
white bread 🍞 ¥168
baguette 🥖 ¥198
MIDARASHI DANGO ¥98
I will get this cinnamon roll for my breakfast ¥170
what else should I get…
my favorite cup noodle 🤩
Tom Yum Kun from Nisshin ¥168
this is the easiest way to settle my craving for Tom Yam Kun
I will store up 3 !
done shopping today and hurry to go home
my husband is getting better
I come to supermarket to buy groceries
broccoli 🥦 ¥148
carrot 🥕 ¥158
boiled Udon ¥88
TAKANA (pickled mustard green) ¥297
fresh cream ¥288
sausage ¥248
slice cheese ¥178
cottage cheese ¥418
cheese (that can be tear off) ¥178
cream cheese ¥388
I have a list in my hand because there are something I can’t miss today
potato chips with potato (HIKARU) 🥔 from Hokkaido ¥108
this used potato Snow March 🥔 also from Hokkaido ¥108
pretz ¥88
what is this?
🐛 gummy?
let’s get it for fun 🎃
vanilla ice cream 🍨 ¥358
frozen EDAMAME ¥198
done shopping 🎶